♪ It seems today that all you see ♪
♪ Is violence in movies
and sex on TV ♪
♪ But where are those good
old-fashioned values ♪
♪ On which we used to rely? ♪
♪ Lucky there's a family guy ♪
♪ Lucky there's a man
who positively can do ♪
♪ All the things that make us ♪
♪ Laugh and cry ♪
♪ He's... a... Fam... ily... Guy! ♪
Ah, the Feast of San Gennaro.
Every child here has seen a relative
murdered in a barber chair.
Step right up!
Teach an old Italian
lady how to use an iPad!
Now, that sounds like
fun. I'll give it a try.
Hey, how are you? Look
what I got for you.
What is it? It's a tablet computer.
I don't want it.
But you don't even know what it is.
But you can watch movies on it.
My eyes hurt.
I'm trying to do something nice here!
For the last time, I don't want it.
I bet you if Joey was giving
it to you, you'd take it.
Don't you bring him into this.
Joey was a good boy.
Oh, yeah, yeah, Joey was a good boy?
You thought he was making 100
grand a year hauling lumber?
Don't you start with this.
He was dirty, Ma!
I can't hear this! I won't hear it!
- He was an angel!
- Oh, that's right.
"Angel Joey," great
Joey, perfect Joey.
I got to go to the church.
Oh, yeah, sure, light another candle.
That'll bring him back.
You watch your tongue.
Admit it, you wish it was me
in that car instead of him!
Just take your little TV and go!
It's an iPad, you dumb cow!
I guess I don't have any sons now.
Ma! I'm sorry, Ma!
Ma! Ma!
Hey, Bri, look over there.
That guy looks like Frank Sinatra, Jr.
Stewie, this is Federal Hill.
Everybody looks like
Frank Sinatra, Jr.
Well, then who's that guy
who looks like a young Frank Sinatra?
Oh, that's Woody Allen's
son, but you're right,
that other guy behind him
is Frank Sinatra, Jr.
Stewie! Elliot!
It-it's actually Brian.
We've-we've met many times before.
Then who's Elliot?
I-I really wouldn't know.
This is a bad start to
whatever we're doing.
Well, now, what brings you
fellas to the festival?
My dad will drive long
distances for ice
with colored liquid in it.
They got blue!
And we all love the Italian food.
Oh, you like Italian food?
Want a meatball?
Yeah, I'm gonna pass on
that, but it's a shame
we can't get good Italian
food like this in Quahog.
Well, maybe the three
of us ought to open
an Italian restaurant there.
Open our own Italian restaurant?
I say, that sounds fun.
You, uh, you keep
meatballs in your jacket?
Oh, yeah, all my pockets are
lined with Reynolds Wrap.
I learned that from my old buddies:
Dean Martin, Jr., Joey Bishop, Jr.,
and Sammy Davis the Third.
Hey, where's Chris?
He's over there playing
that carnival game.
Step right up!
Everybody take a chance
on Whack-a-Big-a-Pussy!
Hey, Ton'!
This is not what I thought it was!
Oh, my God, Chris is out of control!
I know!
It must be all the violence
in movies and sex on TV.
Oh.
See, I listen.
Peter, we need to talk
about what happened
at the street fair.
Lois, it's an Italian festival.
You're supposed to yell "Bella, Bella"
and grab as much fat ass as you can.
No, I'm talking about Chris.
I had no idea he had so
much pent-up aggression.
We have to deal with his anger
issues before he hurts himself.
Ah, that's good thinking, Lois.
I've seen what happens
when people hold in their
aggression for too long.
Don't forget, I was in
that elevator with Jay-Z.
Hey, could you have
your guy hit "two"?
I got to get down to
the business center
to print out my boarding pass.
Oh! Hey! That's gonna leave a mark!
That's from a movie.
So, you girls traveling
with your dad here?
Hey, don't kick him, Muddy Shoes.
He's got a white suit on.
Hey, look, I don't know if you
guys are really staying here,
but you can't get into the
pool without a room key.
Okay, Chris, your mom
and I want to help you
get out some of that aggression,
so I thought you and me
could huck rotten
apples at passing cars.
Oh, I didn't know we had
brown apple in the forecast.
Welp, we needed it.
Wow, can I have a turn?
Hey, which one of you threw
that apple at my car?
He did it. He dragged me out here.
I wanted to be in school, sir.
Where'd you get a
cannon like that, kid?
I work out my right arm
three times a day.
Mm, Free weights?
No, mostly JPEGs of Helen
Hunt on my hard drive.
Well, I'm Coach Doyle, and I
head up the baseball team
at James Woods High.
What fake class do they
also make you teach?
- Driver's ed, right?
- No, wood shop.
Ah, that was my second guess.
Tell me, son, how would
you like to pitch
for the high school team?
Baseball's the sport people
play while eating, right?
Oh, yeah, sometimes I even
watch a whole Blacklist.
I don't know, I've never
played baseball before.
Oh, come on, Chris, you got to do it.
If you don't, you'll regret it.
Just like Jesus' friend, Evan,
who bailed on the Last Supper.
Aw, they did a painting?
I would've gone if I knew they
were gonna do a painting.
Here we are, fellas.
The future site of Quahog's
newest Italian restaurant.
Wow, this is a great location.
Can we afford this?
Sure we can.
I set up one of those Kickstarters.
Then I realized how stupid that is
and I went to the bank for
a loan like an adult.
Now, fellas, the tables should
all be bolted to the floor
to prevent theft.
You know, most restaurants
go out of business
because people are
stealing the tables.
The toilets should also
be bolted to the floor.
I think that's pretty
standard, Frank, but okay.
Great. Now let's go find
some chump's restaurant
and steal his tables and toilets.
James Woods is winning for
now, but y'all never know
what might happen in
the moments to come.
I mean, look, there's
two baseball guys
out on the bases right now.
What if they's run to
the scoring place?
Oh, here comes a new boy.
All right, Chris!
Wow, I've never seen him
run onto a baseball field
when he wasn't chasing a duck
or being chased by a duck.
That a duck over there?
Ah, come on!
What the hell's Coach Doyle thinking
bringing in that fat slob?!
You know what?
I bet you a hundred bucks that
"fat slob" strikes this kid out.
Ha, you're on.
Strike one!
Strike two!
Ooh!
Strike three!
Three strikes and he's out,
just like my cousin
Freddie with the drugs.
Holy crap, a hundred bucks!
Hey, nice going, Chris!
Wow, look how proud my dad is.
Oh, my God, a duck!
It was a trap!
Guys, tonight the drinks are on me.
I just won a hundred bucks
off Chris's baseball game.
Really? How'd you do that?
This dad took one look at
Chris and thought he'd suck,
but it turns out Chris
is a great pitcher.
I'm so proud of the money
I won betting on him.
You know, I bet there are
plenty of other baseball dads
who'd also assume Chris stinks.
Peter, we could make a lot of money.
Yeah, we could make
Toni Braxton money.
Is that... is that a lot?
It's a lot, and then nothing.
And then a record whose proceeds
go directly to creditors.
♪ Put me in, Coach ♪
♪ I'm ready to play ♪
♪ Today ♪
♪ Put me in, Coach ♪
♪ I'm ready to play ♪
♪ Today ♪
♪ Look at me ♪
♪ I can be ♪
♪ Centerfield ♪
♪ Well, I spent some time
in the Mudville Nine ♪
♪ Watching it from the bench ♪
♪ You know I took some lumps ♪
♪ When the Mighty Casey struck out ♪
♪ So Say Hey Willie ♪
♪ Tell the Cobb ♪
♪ And Joe DiMaggio ♪
♪ Don't say it ain't so ♪
♪ You know the time is now. ♪
Frank, where the hell is everybody?
This was supposed to be
our big opening night.
I'll tell you what the problem is.
Every successful restaurant
has a hook or a gimmick.
That's what we're lacking.
No, we're not.
Frank, you're the hook! That's right.
We just need to make you the
face of the restaurant.
It may be the five
loaves of garlic bread
I ate this morning talking, but
I think that's a swell idea.
♪ You'll love the meal ♪
♪ The fancy feel ♪
♪ The showbiz stories
while you eat your veal ♪
♪ It's family dining
with a mobster feel ♪
♪ At Frank Sinatra's restaurant ♪
Junior!
♪ The wine is red ♪
♪ With lots of bread ♪
And portions bigger
than a horse's head.
♪ You'll burp up sausages
tonight in bed ♪
♪ At Frank Sinatra's restaurant ♪
♪ Here's a toast ♪
♪ To our host ♪
♪ The food's not great, but ♪
♪ Drink enough and you won't know ♪
♪ The guests will swoon
and Frank will croon ♪
♪ A "beep-bop-dooby-dop"
Italian tune ♪
♪ You dine like royalty ♪
♪ At Frank Sinatra's restaurant ♪
♪ We got big plans
to please our fans ♪
♪ Our cocktail waitress
has enormous cans ♪
♪ A men's room servant who
will dry your hands ♪
♪ At Frank Sinatra's restaurant ♪
♪ Our pizza pies could win a prize ♪
♪ The jukebox catalog is double size ♪
♪ It plays both Capitol
and, yes, Reprise ♪
That's "Repreeze."
♪ At Frank Sinatra's restaurant ♪
♪ Gorgeous views ♪
♪ And top-shelf booze ♪
♪ Yes, we serve Jews ♪
♪ Um, that was never an issue ♪
♪ So, raise your glass ♪
♪ You'll have a gas ♪
♪ But seating's limited,
so move your ass ♪
♪ And plant it firmly ♪
♪ Here at Frank Sinatra's restaurant ♪
♪ Frank's restaurant ♪
♪ Frank's res... taurant. ♪
Wow!
Look at this, guys.
I can't believe we made
all this in one game.
Yeah, I'm having a great time
handling this money and
then touching my eyeball.
Jerome, another round
for my blurry friends.
Yeah, we got a good thing going.
We just have to keep
Chris's talent a secret.
Good evening, I'm Tom Tucker.
Our top story tonight, the
James Woods High baseball team
is headed to the
district championship,
thanks to their secret weapon,
star pitcher Chris Griffin.
Ah, crap, now everyone
knows Chris is a ringer!
Tom Tucker just ruined everything.
This sucks even worse than
when I stubbed my toe.
Aah!
Why does everything bad
always happen to me?!
Answer me, guy in box
and guy on cross!
Stewie, can I talk to you?
Look, Brian, I affectionately
pat all the waiters on the ass.
And if anyone has a problem with it,
they should come to me directly!
No, no, it's not that.
I-I've been going
through our receipts,
and we're actually losing money.
Well, yeah, duh.
Frank comps every meal.
Look, he's doing it again.
Little-known secret
about Charlton Heston.
Never used toilet paper.
Just drop and go.
Uh, here, let me get
that check for you.
Well, it's official.
Nobody wants to bet against Chris now.
Damn it! I can't believe my kid
isn't making money for us anymore.
I feel like Jessica Simpson's dad.
Well, there are plenty
of guys willing to bet
on James Woods High to
win, I'll tell you that.
The only way we could ever make
money now is if Chris lost.
Wait a minute, Joe, that's it!
All we got to do is take those bets
and get Chris to take a dive!
Wait, hold on, Peter.
You're gonna ask your own
son to lose on purpose?
Damn, Quagmire!
Your fridge gives you
water from the door?
Hey, champ, what you doing?
My Spanish homework.
Oh, well, then maybe I'll just
say this to you in Spanish.
_
Chris, what the hell are you doing?!
Calm down. This is how
they package Snapple now.
They're trying to trick
kids into drinking it.
You may not believe this,
but there was a time when
Snapple ruled the nation.
Preposterous!
It's true. Even Jerry
Seinfeld drank it.
And he was the president of the '90s.
But why are you so down?
Dad told me I have to lose the
championship game on purpose.
He what?!
Peter, get in here right now!
Wow, someone's day-horny!
Oh, hey, Chris.
Did you tell Chris he had to lose
the district championship?!
Let me just get a
garbage bag. Hold on.
Okay, now that I'm decent.
Yes, I did tell Chris
to throw the game.
But it's okay; it's for gambling.
What?! You're betting on
Chris's baseball team?!
Technically against
Chris's baseball team.
Are you crazy?!
Do I look crazy?!
What do you think puts
the food on our table
and the garbage bags on our backs?!
Chris, your father's a jackass.
When you get on that field,
you try your very
best and play to win.
You understand me?
Yeah. Thanks, Mom.
But, Lois, if Chris wins that game,
I'll be out a ton of money and
I'll have to kiss a fella!
I take all kinds of bets.
Hey, Frank, we have to talk.
You've got to stop giving
away all the food for free.
Yeah, otherwise there's no way
we're gonna make a profit.
Oh, we don't have to
worry about money.
I might be doing a Duets
thing with that Lady Goo-Ga.
Uh-huh, that's wrong.
Anyway, the restaurant's
gonna go under
if you keep giving away food.
All right, all right.
Thank you, Frank.
I appreciate you trying it my way.
Thank you.
What was that?
Oh, I get 40 bucks
every time somebody says "my way."
Nancy gets 60.
What do you mean Chris
won't take a dive?!
We already took a ton of bets!
Look, I'm sorry, you guys,
but my hot piece-of-ass
wife says no way.
It's a weird time to brag
about your wife, Peter.
I don't know, I've just
been so horny today.
Oh, man, I don't need to know that!
Well, pull it together, Peter,
'cause we're about to
lose a lot of money!
I know.
We're screwed once
Chris takes the mound
with that awesome arm of his.
Wait, so what you're saying
is Chris isn't the problem,
his arm is.
I guess.
Okay. We hear you, Peter.
Loud and clear.
Yeah, we'll fix this problem.
You guys are creeping me out.
All right, I'm gonna
exit while discreetly
checking out the hot
chick by the door.
You guys heard what I heard, right?
Peter just asked us
to break Chris's arm.
Well, he intimated.
I don't know what that means,
but let's go rough up a
teenager for beer money!
Oh, I call biting!
Okay, there's the baseball
team's locker room right there.
Perfect! And we look like
regular high school students,
so we'll fit right in.
Joe, are you sure about these clothes?
Trust me. I bought the absolute
latest issue of Archie comics,
and this is what the kids are wearing.
Oh, hey, fellow teens.
Wait a minute, teenagers
don't have wheelchairs!
No! Oh, no!
Okay, guys, we've served
our last free meal.
Here I go with the check.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Last time we ate here,
Mr. Sinatra's son said it was free.
Okay, uh, everyone, new policy!
As is the case with many restaurants,
you're going to have
to pay for your food.
What? This food ain't
worth paying for.
Yeah, the only reason we eat
here is 'cause it's free.
Look whose restaurant
thinks it's so good!
Oh, yeah? If it was Joey's
restaurant, you would've paid.
Ma!
I'm sorry, Ma!
I can't believe it.
They hated us.
Well, fellas, we gave
it our best shot.
If you need me, I'll be
back in Palm Springs,
which has been completely
taken over by the gays.
So, want to grab whatever wine is left
and then burn the place down?
Maybe, but first, let's
have an unearned
end-of-the-series moment
where we turn out the lights
on our own place.
Sorry, pal, we're closed.
Peter, we've got great news!
Chris isn't playing!
He's not? Why?
Well, 'cause we broke his
arm like you told us to.
Shattered. We shattered his arm.
You what?! I never
told you to do that!
You didn't? That's what
I thought I heard.
Quagmire, this is humbling,
but it may be time
for all of us to talk
about hearing aids.
I feel terrible! I got
to go find my son!
Chris!
Dad, my arm's broke!
And look, a Camaro!
Oh, that guy must be so boss.
But listen, Chris, I had no
idea this was gonna happen.
Look, I was wrong to
bet on your games,
and it's even worse that
I told you to lose.
I'm so sorry.
Oh, that's okay, Dad.
I just feel bad that my arm is broken
in so many places and hurts so much.
No, Chris, I've been a
terrible dad lately.
You found something you were great at,
and instead of being happy for you,
I tried to use it to make money.
And now your arm is broken and
your baseball career is over.
Not necessarily.
What? What are you talking about?
Well, for the last few
weeks, since my right arm's
been exhausted from pitching,
my left arm's had to, uh,
pick up the slack in the bathroom.
You see the pitcher?
That's my kid.
Aah! Son of a bitch!
Oh, my God!
Sorry, Mr. Quagmire!
I heard that bone break.
My ears are fine.
Well, Chris, we're very proud of you
for making it to the
district championship.
Thanks, Mom.
It was really something, Lois.
The next pitch Chris threw
hit his coach in the head,
so there was no one to
take him out of the game.
Chris walked the next 46 batters.
State record.
Wow, Chris! State record!
Yeah, they got crushed.
But at least I didn't have to pay out
all those bets and kiss a guy.
But I saw you kissing the
driver of that Camaro.
That... that-that was something else.
Baseball!
Thank you for watching "Family Guy" on
www.FOX-fan.ru